http://www.appointmentquest.com/privacy

AppointmentQuestOverviewDemo PricingSupportContactSign inFree trialAppointmentQuest Privacy StatementAppointmentQuest is committed to protecting your privacy.Please take a moment to read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our services. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. The privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.appointmentquest.com website. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us by e-mail at privacy@appointmentquest.com.Information CollectionAppointmentQuest is the sole owner of the information collected on www.appointmentquest.com. AppointmentQuest collects information from our users at several different points on our website. AppointmentQuest explicitly asks when it needs information that personally identifies you pertinent to the specific services you are choosing to subscribe to on the AppointmentQuest website. This information can include your e-mail address, name, postal address, telephone number, and credit card information, as applicable. AppointmentQuest also may ask for non-personal information, business contact information or demographic information.RegistrationIn order to use services provided by AppointmentQuest website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to provide business contact information, such as first and last name, company name, address, phone number and e-mail address as well as to choose username and password. We use this information to establish customer account to provide the user with services on our site for which he has expressed interest. We also require a user’s credit card number to establish regular online scheduling account or partner account. Credit card is not required in order to establish free trial account or affiliate account.SubscriptionWe request information from the user on our accounts enrollment and partner enrollment forms. New users must provide contact information, such as such as first and last name, company name, address, phone number and e-mail address as well as billing information, such as credit card number, expiration date, cardholder name and billing address. This information is used for automated billing purposes. If we have trouble processing account subscription payments, the information is used to contact the user.Information UseAppointmentQuest and AppointmentQuest service partners use your personal information to operate AppointmentQuest website and to provide AppointmentQuest services you have requested. The information is also used to communicate with you regarding your AppointmentQuest accounts when such communication is essential to the operation of the service. You may not opt-out from communications deemed essential to the operation of the service other than by terminating your services with AppointmentQuest. We also use your e-mail address to respond to incoming service and support requests from you, to collect customer feedback, and to perform customer satisfaction surveys. We do not use your e-mail address, postal address, or phone numbers for promotional communications.AppointmentQuest may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on AppointmentQuest; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of AppointmentQuest or the users of AppointmentQuest services; or, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of AppointmentQuest services or the public.Personally identifiable information collected by AppointmentQuest may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which AppointmentQuest or its partners, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.Information SecurityAppointmentQuest secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. AppointmentQuest secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access. All sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number and other financial information) is stored in encrypted data format.When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information, such as credit card number and other financial information, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - Secure Socket Layer (SSL). While on a secure page, such as our enrollment form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’.While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices and data center space. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, all our employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every time new policies are added, all of our employees are notified. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment within controlled access facility, locked in private cabinets.Testimonial DisclosureWe post customer testimonials on our website at www.appointmentquest.com/testimonials. Customer testimonials may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name, business name, city, state, and web address. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their personally identifiable information along with their testimonial.Changes to Personal InformationIf a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as company name, phone, e-mail, postal address, etc.), or if a user no longer desires AppointmentQuest services, we provide a way to correct, update or deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. To review and update your personal contact information, login to your account at www.appointmentquest.com and go to Account Setup Center. AppointmentQuest partners can update their contact information by logging into their partner account at www.appointmentquest.com/partner and clicking on the Partner Business Profile link. If you would like to review other personal information that AppointmentQuest may have about you, e-mail us at privacy@appointmentquest.com.ConfidentialityAppointmentQuest is committed to keeping user’s personally identifiable information confidential. AppointmentQuest never shares service provider schedules with anyone except the service provider's authorized personnel. For users scheduling appointments with a service provider, AppointmentQuest does not share their personal schedule information with anyone except the service provider with whom they make an appointment. All customer contact information and appointment information is kept confidential. Service providers can only view information related to their own appointments.No CookiesA cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. AppointmentQuest website does not use cookies. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you still will be able to fully experience the interactive features of the AppointmentQuest website and AppointmentQuest online scheduling services.Some of our affiliate partners use cookies on our site to indicate referral source. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for referral. Referral cookies do not contain personally identifiable information.No Third Party AdvertisingWe do not allow third party advertising on AppointmentQuest website.No Web BeaconsWe do not use web beacons or other user movement tracking tools on AppointmentQuest website.Log FilesLike most standard website servers we use log files. This includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses and other log elements are not linked to personally identifiable information. Service AnnouncementsOn very rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an e-mail. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, service related communications are not promotional in nature.Customer ServiceWe communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via e-mail or phone, in accordance with the user's wishes and AppointmentQuest customer communication practices.Legal DisclaimerThough we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on AppointmentQuest or www.appointmentquest.com website.Web LinksAppointmentQuest website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, AppointmentQuest, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by www.appointmentquest.com website.Surveys and Feedback RequestsFrom time-to-time AppointmentQuest requests information from users via surveys and feedback requests. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information only. Contact information will be used only to facilitate communication between AppointmentQuest and survey participants. Anonymous survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of AppointmentQuest services. Users’ personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users’ personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.AgentsAppointmentQuest uses a credit card processing company to bill you for services. Credit card transactions are processed by Authorize.Net, which has confidentiality of transactions covered by their privacy policy. Authorize.Net performs secure encrypted credit card transactions for thousands of companies and has stringent security measures in place. Authorize.Net does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any purposes other than processing credit card transactions.ChildrenAppointmentQuest does not intend to collect any personally identifiable information from individuals under the age of 13. Children should always request permission from their parent or guardian prior to submitting their personal information online. If a child has provided AppointmentQuest with personally identifiable information, child's parent or guardian should contact us if they would like to request such information to be deleted from AppointmentQuest records. We will make all reasonable efforts to remove personally identifiable information of the child from AppointmentQuest files and databases.Notification of ChangesIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the news page, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our website for 30 days. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Statement to be informed of how AppointmentQuest is protecting your information.Contact InformationIf you have any questions or suggestions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at:AppointmentQuest LLCP.O. Box 667Broomfield, CO 80038-0667USAprivacy@appointmentquest.comwww.appointmentquest.comLast updated: October 20, 2017 (10/20/2017)
